celebritiesforcharity.org 2015-10-18

# Privacy Policy | Celebrities For Charity

**Overview**

The Celebrities For Charity Foundation is committed to safeguarding your privacy. CFC is the sole owner of and the only organization that uses the information collected on this site. Under no circumstances, unless required by law or ordered to do so by a court of competent jurisdiction, will CFC ever share information collected on this site. Moreover, CFC will never, under any circumstances, sell or rent information collected on this site to others. Furthermore, CFC will never utilize information collected on this site to add the provider of this information to CFC's mail list or to solicit the provider for donations.

Back to Top

**"Cookies"**

Other than the specific instances outlined in this policy, CFC does not collect personal information about users or how they use this site. CFC also does not use the information-tracking devices made possible through "cookies," small pieces of data that may be sent to your Web browser from a server and stored on your computer's hard drive.

Back to Top

**Online Donations**

When making a donation, CFC collects the following Donor information through CFC's secure online financial-transaction pages: name, address, e-mail address, phone number, and credit card information. While the Donor's credit card information is used only to effect the transaction, and is never stored, the remaining personally identifiable information is used to create a receipt for the Donor's donation, which is required for tax purposes, and it is also stored by CFC for its own financial records.

Back to Top

**Online Auctions**

When making a bid on a CFC online auction item, you will be transferred to the website of eBay, Inc. Any information you provide at the eBay website is subject to eBay's Privacy Policy and not CFC's Privacy Policy. If you have any privacy concerns regarding the information you are asked to provide to eBay, you should review eBay's Privacy Policy prior to submitting this information. eBay's Privacy Policy is readily available on their website.

Back to Top

**Online Raffles**

When ordering raffle tickets, CFC collects the following Entrant information through CFC's secure online order entry system: name, address, e-mail address, phone number, and credit card information. While the Entrant's credit card information is used only to effect the transaction, and is never stored, the remaining personally identifiable information is used to create a receipt for Entrant's purchase and to conduct the raffle. Moreover, CFC also stores the Entrant's information for its own records.

In addition to this, if the Entrant chooses to gift his or her tickets to another person, CFC, also through its secure online order entry system, collects the following information about the Gift Recipient: name, address, e-mail address, and phone number. This personally identifiable information is used, if asked to do so by the Entrant, to inform the Gift Recipient of the Entrant's gift and to conduct the raffle. Moreover, CFC also stores the Entrant's information for it own records.

Furthermore, with regard to the Winner of the Raffle, the Entrant, and by acceptance of the gift, the Gift Recipient, pursuant the Official Rules, grant CFC, the Prize Sponsors and their agents permission, without further notice or compensation, to use the Entrant's name and or likeness for purposes of advertising and trade. In addition to this, CFC is also required to provide the Winner's information to the State and local authorities from which CFC received its permit to conduct the Raffle, and to Federal and State taxing authorities.

Back to Top

**Mailing List**

Although CFC does maintain an electronic mailing list, personal information collected from this website is not and never will be added to CFC's mail list.

Back to Top

**Child Safety**

The CFC website has been designed to comply with all applicable child protection laws and guidelines including, but not limited to, The Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 and The Children's Advertising Review Unit (CARU) guidelines, including its guidelines on internet advertising. All of CFC's marketing efforts, including this website, are closely scrutinized to conform to these requirements and guidelines. While CFC makes every effort to make children's visits to its website safe and enjoyable, CFC encourages parents to monitor their children's online usage, and to help CFC protect their privacy by instructing them never to provide personal information on this or any other site without their parent's permission.

Back to Top

**Links to Other Websites**

CFC's site includes links, some temporary and some permanent, to other websites. CFC is not responsible for the privacy and security practices of any other website or the nature of the content contained therein.

Back to Top

**Changes to This Policy**

In the event that CFC decides to alter its privacy policy, the changes will be added directly to this statement. We will, however, always use information in accordance with the version of the privacy policy under which it was originally collected.

Back to Top

**Privacy Questions and Concerns**

If you have specific questions or concerns regarding CFC's privacy policy, please contact us at the following address:

Mail: | Celebrities For Charity Foundation, Inc.  
38 Main Street  
Andover, MA 01810  
---|---  
  
Back to Top
